All right. And so for our fourth project,
the Policy Diff Tool, this was one of
the build concepts provided by
the hosts of the Build-a-thon.
So, for this one, what are we trying
to solve? We're just trying to solve
the discrepancies between policy changes
in two different pairs of policies.
And where I can see this being used or
where we can see this being used is in,
you know, policy updates and more.
So here we just input the first policy
and then the updated policy or the new
version. Here we also have the upload
buttons here if you want to drag and drop.
Then we go ahead and submit the diff.
And so what's going on right now
is that the LLM is processing both texts
side by side. And then later
it will surface the operational changes
and rank them by severity.
And some of the scope decisions and next
steps will be discussed after we go
through results. So as you can see,
12 changes were found: 8 rewords,
3 terms added, and 1 removed.
So here we can see just an overview
of the differences: nine that matter,
1, 2, 3... everything else that's
changed. And that's it for this project.
We scoped to a single-page document
with an upload feature as well as
pasting text. For future iterations, we
might look at potentially grabbing live
policy documents from a website or API
and doing diff based on that.